

Valló Gábor

Junior frontend developer

PERSONAL DATA

Date of birth 17.04.1978

Citizenship Hungarian

E-mail gvallo78@gmail.com

GitHub demo page beren432.github.io

INTRODUCTION

After 20 years of teaching, I got to love programming. I'm attracted to creative challenges and I'd like to commit myself to developing webpages. I'm also interested in backend, my goal is to eventually become a full-stack developer.

HOBBIES

Writing novels
Boardgames

EDUCATION

2022-2023

RUANDER OKTATÓKÖZPONT <u>Junior Frontend Developer</u> course – **vocational exam** (excellent result)

2022

<u>Újratervezés 3.0</u> (4 weeks foundation course)

2005-continually

Training courses in pedagogy & teaching of history.

1997-2003

ELTE BTK; History major & history teacher

1997-2000

ELTE BTK; English language teacher

SKILLS

Languages and frameworks

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap – advanced level Javascript, JQuery, Typescript – medium level Angular, NodeJS, Git, MySQL, React, PHP – basic level **Soft skills**

Creativity, reliability, working independently and in teams, precision, resilience, patience.

LANGUAGES

English – advanced level **German** – writing/understanding medium, speaking basic l.

WORK HISTORY

History teacher:

2019 to current

ÚJPESTI BRÓDY IMRE GIMNÁZIUM ÉS ÁLTALÁNOS ISKOLA (Bp.)

2014-2019

VÁCI MADÁCH IMRE GIMNÁZIUM (Vác)

2003-2014

VARGA ISTVÁN KERESKEDELMI, KÖZGAZDASÁGI SZAKKÖZÉP- ÉS SZAKISKOLA (Bp.)

Main professional activities and achievements:

- ✓ Leadership of history teachers' team
- ✓ Reaching Pedagógus II level
- ✓ Graduation exams at medium and advanced levels
- Teaching adults in evening classes
- ✓ Special history classes for interested students
- Preparation of students for regional and national contests
- ✓ <u>DigiTöri blog</u> (digital history course for 9-11th grades)

Translator:

2007-2012

GENERAL PRESS KIADÓ (Bp.)

My published translations:

Harmadik lehetőség (2007), Napóleon piramisai (2008), Marco Polo (2008), Babilon (2008), A rosette-i kő (2009), A dakotakód (2010), A druidák (2010), Paul Newman (2010), A berber kalózok (2011), Kolumbusz (2012)